(Howard:)Shall we synchronize our watches?
(Leonard:)Guys, there are four of us
and one of him.
(Sheldon:)Which means his triumph
will be even larger.
(Sheldon:)Minstrels will write songs about him.
(Leonard:)Okay, how about this? I'll do the talking,
you stand behind me and try to look...
(Leonard:)...formidable.
(Raj:)I should've peed before we left.
(Kurt:)Yeah?
- Hi, Kurt.
- Lenny, right?
(Leonard:)I don't really go by Lenny,
but that's okay. Um...
(Leonard:)You remember Sheldon, Howard and Raj.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Kurt:)- What do you want?
- You don't remember me?
- How could he not remember?
- Sheldon, not now.
(Sheldon:)I remember him.
(Leonard:)Okay, here it is.
Penny's in kind of a financial jam...
...and the money you owe her would
go a long way to solving her problems.
- And she sent you to get it from me?
- No, she's too proud to ask for the money.